



Mikhail Makarov

Date of birth: 06/05/1993 | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:** (+7) 9651567895 (Mobile) |

Email address: mikhail.makarov@phystech.edu | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/mikmakarov

Telegram: t.me/R0b1nH00d | **Website:** https://mikhailernstovich.github.io

ABOUT ME

I am a software engineer specializing in front-end application development. With a proven track record of creating visually stunning and user-friendly websites, coupled with a passion for clean and efficient coding, I am excited about the opportunity to contribute my skills and expertise to your team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/09/2022 - CURRENT Moscow, Russia

SOFTWARE ENGINEER JSC FLAT

- Created an administrative panel website for the Tretyakov Gallery
- Conducting bug fixing, security updates, migration to new API scheme, and routine maintaining of existing frontend applications
- Implementing new features such as custom photo uploader, complex forms and validation rules
- Working closely with the QA team and backend developer to set up CI/CD on lenkins
- Creating custom stylesheets to match the corporate theme

Website https://flat-soft.ru/

01/09/2016 - CURRENT Zelenograd, Russia

SENIOR RESEARCHER ISC MOLECULAR ELECTRONICS RESEARCH INSTITUTE

- · Carring out theoretical and numerical simulations of different integrated optics devices using Comsol Multiphysics
- Working as a technical expert on neural network accelerators, photonic tensor processors and ADCs
- Writing scientific papers and presenting them on conferences
- Communicating with multi-diciplinary teams of scientists, engineers and managers

Website https://www.niime.ru/

DIGITAL SKILLS

JavaScript | TypeScript | Vue.js | HTML | CSS | SASS | SCSS | Vite | webpack | npm | element-plus.js | git | State Management - Vuex, Pinia - Expert | Node.js, Express.js | Vue CLI | Jenkins | SPA and PWA | Vue router | Bootstrap | Google Firebase | Bubblewrap | Microsoft Office

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/09/2014 - 01/08/2016 Dolgoprudny, Russia

MASTER OF SCIENE (APPLIED MATHEMATICS AND PHYSICS) Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology (MIPT)

Website https://eng.mipt.ru/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2